It's clearly written in black and white.
I want a divorce.
Say it again.
As long as you can do it,
the Su family
will be safe and sound.
I said it.
Su Yuejiao,
you...
Impulsive,
bad-tempered,
and you hurt me when you hit me.
I've had enough.
I want a divorce.
Don't be silly.
Let's go home and talk about it.
Go home?
That's not my home.
We're fake.
All we have
is fake.
It seems that you have forgotten.
Fine.
I'll help you recall.
You just wanted to be the wife of the Commander,
and I wanted to attend the Star Conference.
So you pretended to be my wife,
and I pretended to be your husband.
From the beginning,
we were just working together.
Anyway,
I will marry no one but you.
I like you.
Because I like you,
I care about
whether you really want to divorce me.
I don't want to divorce you.
I want to spend the rest of my life with you.
What about what you said in Yun Bridge?
You said you would marry me.
You said
you would spend the rest of your life with me.
Were those lies?
Those were just
words to make a woman happy.
I've said that to every girl in the pleasure quarters.
Are you
that naive?
Did you fall for it?
Yes,
I did.
Makes sense.
With my talent,
there are so many girls who are interested in me.
But I can't marry them all.
My body
can't handle it.
I don't believe it.
Did they force you to say this?
No one forced me.
Su Yuejiao,
we are not the same kind of people.
Now I'm the top of the Xingyun List.
Who would want to fall back
to the bottom?
To the agency
as a live-in son-in-law?
Listen,
I used to need you,
so I let you bully me.
But now,
Miss Su,
you'd better behave yourself.
Mr. Su,
you've heard enough.
Guards,
see him out.
Thank you, Miss.
Cheng Qi,
I don't believe a word
you said today.
Come back with me.
For old times' sake,
I tried to reason with you.
Mr. Su,
since you're so ungrateful,
I have no choice.
Xiyun,
let's go.
Jiaojiao.
What's wrong?
Have you seen Cheng Qi?
Jiaojiao.
It seems worse than I thought.
Let Cheng Yicheng go and find out.
Cheng Qi,
Jiaojiao is so worried about him,
but when the Escort Agency is in trouble,
he can't wait to find a better one.
He's ungrateful.
I'm afraid
it's not that simple.
It's all your fault.
You said Cheng Qi was Jiaojiao's destiny,
but it's a disaster.
I shouldn't have supported him.
I've always said that Cheng Qi
is no good.
It's a good thing he's gone.
If it weren't for the tricks my uncle played,
my lord wouldn't have been so desperate
to bring in such a disaster.
Right, right.
It's all my fault.
Then I'll find a good match
for your lord in the future.
Is that okay?
Forget it.
Just let her be alone.
I think this time
she is hurt more
than any other time.
She has been lying here for three days.
How can she not eat or drink?
I'll drag her up.
I remember
when we had a quarrel,
she locked herself in the room for three days,
and then knelt in the ancestral hall all night,
and then went to escort.
How about
we take her to the ancestral hall?
Jiao,
you look upset.
Mom,
how could he become like this?
I can't tell the truth
from the false.
Some things
can't be solved by thinking.
You can't get stuck in a rut.
You have to solve it.
Mom,
when dad let you down,
how did you solve it?
To be honest,
I haven't encountered
this situation before.
But if it happens,
just solve it.
Fight with him,
beat him up,
and it's done.
But if you can't bear to do that,
just do what you should do.
The heart of a person
is always so small.
When someone new comes in,
the old ones
will be pushed out.
Mom,
I'm so tired.
I know.
Take a nap.
When you wake up,
everything will be fine.
Dinner's ready.
How long are you going to keep this up?
You're the top scholar
from the Yun State.
I can help you
get a position in the court.
I can give you anything you want.
I'm hungry.
I just want
to eat now.
You said you wanted to make money
and settle in the capital.
Now,
you're living in a big house,
surrounded by beauties,
and having everything served on a silver platter.
This is the life of a deity.
I want a talented and creative leader,
not a zombie-like playboy.
Today,
is the day to hand in the script.
If you can't hand it in on time,
the Su family...
Here.
I told you, it's all for the sake of creation.
I didn't lie to you, did I?
This time, you're serious.
Can you let him go?
It's just a few months.
With my brain,
I'll forget him soon.
Good.
You're the master now.
Find a better one.
Did Ling Chen write all these?
Yes.
The others who wrote for him
have been dealt with.
I'll tell the emperor
that I'm the one who changed the winner.
It was my fault.
I almost ruined your plan.
Thankfully, you dealt with it in time.
But we can't keep Cheng Qi
shouldn't be kept in the open.
Just use his talents.
What?
He's moved into your residence?
If you find it inappropriate,
I'll find another place.
Keep him if you like.
He's just a dog.
But if necessary,
you must be ruthless
in ending the relationship.
Yes.
Father, please rest assured.
He's gone,
and he's not coming back.
Su Yuejiao,
just let go of him.
A lot of people are saying we're stealing from ourselves.
All the merchants in Yunxing City
have been taken by Fu Xiang.
What's left
are just small orders.
Gong Xi and I
delivered them all in half a day.
There are only a few short-distance deliveries out of town.
All relying on regular customers.
The situation is worse than I expected.
But don't worry.
I'll figure it out.
What method?
I haven't thought of it yet.
If he were here, he would have a solution.
Put it there.
By the way,
bring me some more wine.
My Lord, it's me.
What are you doing here?
Have you found a new beauty?
I found them according to your preferences.
Come on.
How's the escort agency?
After my Lady went back,
for three days.
She's out these days.
But the agency has no business.
Gong Xi and Facha
come to the Moon God Pavilion to work every day.
She must be holding on.
No.
I have to find a way
to get out of here.
By the way,
did you send the news that I'm messing around to Ning'an?
Rest assured, my lord.
It's very disgusting.
That's good.
The more disgusting it is,
the sooner my father will come.
Remember to
meet my father at the city gate.
Don't go to the wrong place.
I haven't bathed for several days.
Look,
I'm almost covered with mushrooms.
You don't have to pretend to this extent.
Are you stupid?
If I don't do this,
I will be eaten up by Zhang Xi Yun.
It's really tiring to be a playboy.
I'm drinking so much that my liver hurts.
I'd rather be beaten by my wife.
My Lord
Can we go back to the Escort Agency?
As long as I'm alive,
I must go back to find her.
Cheng Qi fell seriously ill.
He offered to step down as the top scholar.
I'm worried
that the Poetry Meeting will be delayed.
I remember Cheng Qi is quite young.
There's no plague in the capital.
What's going on?
He's a free spirit,
living on his own terms.
I didn't want to pry.
What's the illness?
Your Majesty is busy with state affairs.
This trivial matter shouldn't bother you.
How is the new champion
doing?
I've assigned him to draft the speech.
Please review it.
You're truly a lifesaver.
The speech contest
will be your responsibility.
Is it settled?
Yes, sir.
Lord Yue,
assist the Grand Preceptor well.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Do you need escort?
Call your chief escort over.
I'm Su Yuejiao,
the chief escort of Su's Escort Agency.
You're the chief escort?
You're so young and a woman.
I don't think your agency is reliable.
Su's Escort Agency
will deliver the goods.
I'll give it a try.
Good kung fu.
I'll hire you.
You'll get your share of the reward.
Kala Town.
I can't go there.
It's a rule set by my mother.
Kala Town is too far away.
It will take at least
half a month to go there and back.
And it's on the border of Langyue.
But we need the money.
How much did he offer?
It doesn't matter.
Do you remember
how long we were pursued
after escorting to Klak City?
Anyway, we can't go.
Dad and Mom were injured for justice.
And the money earned from this escort
can support the Escort Agency for half a year.
So much?
What are they transporting?
Some treasures purchased in the Yun State.
My Lord, is this a scam?
Or I'll go with you.
I'll protect you.
You are the biggest danger when there is no danger.
No.
I just want to do something for the Agency.
No one is allowed to go.
Stop arguing.
Don't tell Grandpa about this.
Or he will worry about me.
You should go back first.
My Lord,
this is the place.
He's been indulging in debauchery
and revelry in there.
That brat!
I thought he'd settle down
after getting married.
But he has gone further!
Who dares to break into the Prime Minister's Garden?
Call Cheng Qi out!
I'm his father!
Cheng Qi, get out!
Get out! Get out!
You don't let me in, right?
You!
And you!
Cheng Yicheng!
My Lord!
Retreat!
Don't mess with these things anymore.
They're useless.
What do you know?
It's meant to be a brake.
It can control the speed of the carriage.
If it wasn't broken,
the carriage wouldn't be able to move.
Don't you know how strong she is?
Now she's gone, what are we gonna do?
What are you arguing about in the morning?
Where did Jiaojiao go?
15 years ago,
I said you were a glory seeker.
I was too shallow back then.
This drink is my apology to you.
That's not what you said back then.
You said I was just a brown-noser.
At the last autumn hunt,
my horse wasn't spooked.
This drink is to make amends.
I knew it!
You just wanted to see me fall
in front of everyone, didn't you?
Warriors are no match for scholars.
Enough.
Just tell me,
what do you need from me?
You must know about the Star Conference.
Don't mention it.
Your son is well-read
and talented.
But he doesn't look like your son.
I heard
Cheng Qi is seriously ill.
I thought he had returned to Ning'an.
What happened?
Yicheng.
Lord Yue.
What happened to Cheng Qi?
After being invited to the Grand Preceptor's villa,
he never came out.
What was he doing there?
Drinking, listening to music, watching dances.
Just like before in Ning'an.
So he's not sick at all.
How dare the Grand Preceptor deceive the royal family?
What about his wife?
Can she allow him to stay out all night?
Lady Yan went to see him earlier.
He said he wanted to divorce.
I didn't go back to the escort agency.
I don't know the details.
Escort agency?
What... what divorce?
It's not that simple.
Is it that the Grand Preceptor
threatened to use Su Biaotou and the escort agency
to put Cheng Qi under house arrest?
Su Biaotou,
I'm confused.
The poem the Grand Preceptor presented to the Emperor
was somewhat like Cheng Qi's style.
Is he detaining Cheng Qi
to make him write for someone else?
What do you mean by write for someone else?
After all these years,
can't you read more?
It's like
someone forcing you
to use my name
to make you
to please the enemy.
They are simply bullying me too much.
I'll risk my life...
Enough.
You can go in, but you come to me.
Don't you just want me to save him?
Can you save him?
Yes.
What are the conditions?
Three kowtows.
I'll kowtow for the master.
Enough.
You really kneel.
Sit.
I'll save him.
You old thing.
We haven't seen each other for years.
You've learned to be
much slicker.
But don't worry.
The royal family cherishes talents.
We highly value your son.
You're just in time.
Get changed,
and come to the palace with me.
Good.
Let's drink.
Cheers.
I intended to save you,
but Cheng Qi didn't allow it.
I got you into this trouble.
I'm sorry.
It's too late
to say sorry.
Don't hurt people in the future.
Don't waste the life my mother sacrificed for you.
My Lord,
you misunderstood him.
We only rob the rich and cruel,
and never kill anyone.
Shut up.
No matter who you rob,
robbing escorts is not justice.
You're right.
We were wrong.
You can go.
I'll pretend I didn't see anything.
If you get caught by the government,
no one can help you.
I heard you got divorced.
It's none of your business.
I have a long way to go.
Goodbye.
My Lord, you've been waiting for so many days,
just to say these few words?
Follow the escort team.